Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Writings, 1901-2009
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Various Adaptations (proposed abridgements including a young people's edition), 1991-1994, 1999; cuid15566 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Various Adaptations (proposed animation projects), 2005-2008; cuid15567 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Various Adaptations and Formats (proposed website), 1999; cuid15568 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Books: A People's History of the United States - Various Adaptations and Formats (various other proposals), 1995-1999, 2009, undated; cuid15569 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Books: The Politics of History, 1967-1970, 1989; cuid15570 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Books: The Politics of History (Second Edition), 1989-1990; cuid15571 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Books: The Politics of History - Editor's Proof (I), [1970]; cuid15572 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Books: The Politics of History - Editor's Proof (II), [1970]; cuid15573 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Books: The Politics of History - Editor's Proof (III), [1970]; cuid15574 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Books: The Politics of History - Editor's Proof (IV), [1970]; cuid15575 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Books: The Politics of History - Reviews, 1970-1975; cuid15576 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Books: Postwar America: 1945-1971, 1966-1975; cuid15577 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Books: Postwar America: 1945-1971 - Reviews, 1973-1974, undated; cuid15578 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Books: Potential Book of Essays on Abolishing War, with Gino Strada (including email from Arundhati Roy), 2005-2006; cuid15579 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Books: Potential Book of Essays on Abolishing War, with Gino Strada (including fax messages and essay from Nadine Gordimer; also email from Cindy Sheehan), 1997-2006, undated; cuid15580 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Books: A Power That Governments Cannot Suppress, 2005-2008; cuid15581 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Books: A Power That Governments Cannot Suppress - Reviews, 2007-2008; cuid15582 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Books: The Power of Nonviolence, [2002]; cuid15583 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Books: The Rule of Law (Zinn was a contributor) - Review, 1971; cuid15584 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Books: SNCC: The New Abolitionists, [1964]; cuid15585 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Books: SNCC: The New Abolitionists - Reviews, 1964-1965; cuid15586 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Books: The Southern Mystique, 1958-1964, undated; cuid15587 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Books: The Southern Mystique - Correspondence, 1962-1965; cuid15588 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Books: The Southern Mystique - Reviews, 1964-1968, undated; cuid15589 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Books: Terrorism and War, 2003-2005; cuid15590 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Books: Three Plays: The Political Theater of Howard Zinn, 2009, undated; cuid15591 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Books: Three Strikes, 2001; cuid15592 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Books: The Twentieth Century: A People's History, 1981-1983, 2003; cuid15593 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Books: The Twentieth Century: A People's History - Review, 1985; cuid15594 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Books: Uncommon Sense, 2007, 2008; cuid15595 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Books: Vietnam: The Logic of Withdrawal, 1966-1968; cuid15596 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Books: Vietnam: The Logic of Withdrawal, [1967]; cuid15597 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Books: Vietnam: The Logic of Withdrawal - Reviews, 1967-1968; cuid15598 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Books: Vietnam: The Logic of Withdrawal - Reader Actions (includes letters from Edward M. Kennedy and from Edward W. Brooke), 1967; cuid15599 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Books: Voices of a People's History of the United States, 2004-2005, undated; cuid15600 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Books: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train, 1992-1995, [2002]; cuid15601 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Books: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Editor's Proof (I), [1994]; cuid15602 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Books: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Editor's Proof (II), [1994]; cuid15603 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Books: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Reviews, 1994-1996; cuid15604 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Books: A Young People's History of the United States, 2007, 2009; cuid15605 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Books: The Zinn Reader, 1996-2001; cuid15606 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Dissertation: "Conscience of the Jazz Age: LaGuardia in Congress" (personal hand-written card from Mrs. Marie LaGuardia enclosed), 1959, undated; cuid15607 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Drafts and Fragments, undated; cuid15608 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Eulogies: Luria, Salvador (includes correspondence and memorial program), 1991; cuid15609 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1963-2008; cuid15610 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Liner Notes: Fellow Workers (Ani DiFranco), 1999; cuid15611 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Films: "Revolution" (unproduced adaptation of A People's History of the United States, script by Howard Fast), 2000-2002; cuid15612 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Films: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Correspondence, 2003-2005; cuid15613 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Films: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Press, 2003-2004, undated; cuid15614 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Films: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Reviews, 2004; cuid15615 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Films: You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Screenings, 2004-2006, undated; cuid15616 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Pamphlets: Columbus, the Indians, and Human Progress 1492-1992, cuid15617 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Pamphlets: Hiroshima: Breaking the Silence, 1995; cuid15618 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Pamphlets: Power, History and Warfare, 1991-1992; cuid15619 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Pamphlets: Times Square, undated; cuid15620 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Plays: As the World Turns - Productions, Jan 2001-Apr 2001, undated; cuid15621 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Plays: As the World Turns - Script (also includes notes and fragments), undated; cuid15622 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Background, 2001, 2003, 2006; cuid15623 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Correspondence, 1985-1986, 2007-2009, undated; cuid15624 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Notes, undated; cuid15625 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Productions (New York), 1985, undated; cuid15626 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Productions (White Barn Theater, Westport CT), 1986, undated; cuid15627 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Productions (unknown), undated; cuid15628 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Reviews, 1986, 2009; cuid15629 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Daughter of Venus) (I), 2006; cuid15630 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Daughter of Venus) (II), 2006; cuid15631 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Daughter of Venus) (III), 2006; cuid15632 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Daughter of Venus) (IV), 2006; cuid15633 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Daughter of Venus), undated; cuid15634 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Unsafe Distances) (I), undated; cuid15635 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Unsafe Distances) (II), undated; cuid15636 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Plays: Daughter of Venus / Unsafe Distances - Scripts (Unsafe Distances) (III), undated; cuid15637 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Movie Script and Treatment, undated; cuid15638 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (cello), 2005; cuid15639 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (clarinet), 2005; cuid15640 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (general), 2004-2005, undated; cuid15641 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (percussion), 2005; cuid15642 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (piano), 2005; cuid15643 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (piano vocal score), 2005; cuid15644 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (trumpet), 2005; cuid15645 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Opera (violin), 2005; cuid15646 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Rebel in Paradise, 1985-1987, undated; cuid15647 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Rebel in Paradise (poster), [1987]; cuid15648 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Plays: Emma - Adaptations - Red Emma, 1995, undated; cuid15649 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - Almeda Sperry, 1975-1976, undated; cuid15650 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - Exile Letters, undated; cuid15651 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - General, 1981, 1989-1990, 1993, undated; cuid15652 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - Raw Data, 1983, 1985, undated; cuid15653 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - Slide Photos, undated; cuid15654 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Plays: Emma - Background - The True Story of the Assassination of President McKinley at Buffalo by Richard H. Barry, 1901; cuid15655 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Plays: Emma - Correspondence - General, 1976-1991, undated; cuid15656 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Plays: Emma - Final Draft Disk (screenwriting software), 2001; cuid15657 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Plays: Emma - Introduction, undated; cuid15658 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Plays: Emma - Music, 2005, undated; cuid15659 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Plays: Emma - Poster, undated; cuid15660 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Bilbao), 2009; cuid15661 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Bordeaux), 2009; cuid15662 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Boston), 1977, undated; cuid15663 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Boston) - Correspondence, 1977-1978, undated; cuid15664 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Japan), 1990-1991, 2010, undated; cuid15665 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Japan), undated; cuid15666 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Japan) - Poster, undated; cuid15667 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (New York 1986), 1985-1986, undated; cuid15668 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (various), 1986, 1994-2009, undated; cuid15669 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Plays: Emma - Productions (Woodstock), 2004; cuid15670 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Plays: Emma - Readings (Suffolk), 2008; cuid15671 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Plays: Emma - Related Works - E.G. a Musical Portrait of Emma Goldman, 1986, 1994; cuid15672 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Plays: Emma - Reviews (Boston), 1976-1977; cuid15673 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Plays: Emma - Reviews (London), 1987; cuid15674 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Plays: Emma - Reviews (New York), 1986; cuid15675 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Plays: Emma - Reviews (South End Press), 2001, 2003-2005, undated; cuid15676 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Plays: Emma - Reviews (various), 1976, 1979, 1994, undated; cuid15677 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts, undated; cuid15678 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts (French), undated; cuid15679 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts (Japanese), 1990, undated; cuid15680 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts ("later"), undated; cuid15681 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts (London), undated; cuid15682 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts - "New York 1986 Script", cuid15683 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts - "New York Long Script (to 1917)", undated; cuid15684 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Plays: Emma - Scripts - Original, undated; cuid15685 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Background (Bakunin), undated; cuid15686 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Background (Capital), 1942, undated; cuid15687 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Background (Lassalle), undated; cuid15688 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Background (Marx biography), 1984-1987, 1997, undated; cuid15689 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Background (raw data), undated; cuid15690 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - General, 1993, 1999-2003, undated; cuid15691 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Notes, undated; cuid15692 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (Boston), 2000; cuid15693 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (Cuba), 2004-2006; cuid15694 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (Italy), 2007-2009; cuid15695 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (Japan), 2002, undated; cuid15696 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (Tampa), 1998-2000, undated; cuid15697 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (various, abroad), 1993, 1999-2009, undated; cuid15698 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (various, domestic), 1993-2005; cuid15699 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Productions (various, domestic), 2006-2009, undated; cuid15700 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Reviews (productions), 1999-2006, undated; cuid15701 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Reviews (South End Press), 1999-2001, undated; cuid15702 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Scripts, Sep 1988; cuid15703 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Scripts, Jan 1989; cuid15704 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Scripts, Jun 1998; cuid15705 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Scripts (I), undated; cuid15706 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Scripts (II), undated; cuid15707 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Plays: Marx in Soho - Uncorrected Galley Proof of Marx in Soho: A Play on History (South End Press), 1998; cuid15708 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Readings: "The People Speak" - Sundance, Jan 2009; cuid15709 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Readings: "The People Speak" - Voices of Dissent, [2008]; cuid15710 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Readings: A People's History of the United States - Harper Collins Millionth Copy Event, 2002, 2003, undated; cuid15711 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Readings: A People's History of the United States - Harper Collins Millionth Copy Event (correspondence), 2002, 2003, undated; cuid15712 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - 92nd Street Y, May 2009; cuid15713 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Baltimore, Nov 2009; cuid15714 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Berkeley, Nov 2006, undated; cuid15715 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Boston, 2004, undated; cuid15716 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Boulder, 2008, undated; cuid15717 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Cooper Union, 2006; cuid15718 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Cooper Union, May 2007; cuid15719 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Denver, Oct 2007; cuid15720 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Harlem, Dec 2005; cuid15721 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Lannan Foundation, Stanta Fe, New Mexico, 2006, undated; cuid15722 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Los Angeles, 2005, undated; cuid15723 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Los Angeles, 2006, undated; cuid15724 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Minnesota, 2009; cuid15725 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - New York, 2006; cuid15726 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - New York Pubic Lilbrary, Sep 2005; cuid15727 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - New York Small Presses, undated; cuid15728 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - New York Society for Ethical Culture, 2004; cuid15729 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Pasadena, 2007; cuid15730 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Provincetown, 2007; cuid15731 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Raw Material, 2001-2003, undated; cuid15732 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Raw Material, undated; cuid15733 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Recordings, 2005; cuid15734 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Reviews, 2005; cuid15735 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - San Francisco, 2009; cuid15736 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Seattle, undated; cuid15737 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Vassar College, 2005; cuid15738 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Readings: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" - Washington D.C., 2005; cuid15739 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Screenplays: "Purgatory River", 2008; cuid15740 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Screenplays: "Purgatory River" - Working Title, "A Western Story", Oct 1997; cuid15741 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Screenplays: "Purgatory River" - Working Title, "A Western Story", Oct 1997-Nov 1997; cuid15742 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Special Report: Albany, A Study in National Responsibility, 1962; cuid15743 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Speeches: "Academic Freedom: Collaboration and Resistance" The 23rd T.B.Davis Memorial Lecture, University of Cape Town, South Africa, 1982; cuid15744 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Speeches: Christopher Columbus, 1991-1992; cuid15745 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Speeches: Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1989, 1991-1994; cuid15746 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Speeches: France in 2003, 2003-2004; cuid15747 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Speeches: "Just War" (Rome), [2003]; cuid15748 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Speeches: Various, [1957], 1985, 1986, 2005-2009; cuid15749 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Speeches: Vietnam War, 1966-1971, undated; cuid15750 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Tapings: "The People Speak" - Actor Brochure, 2007-2008; cuid15751 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Tapings: "The People Speak" - Audience Reactions, 2005, undated; cuid15752 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Tapings: "The People Speak" - Boston, Jan 2009; cuid15753 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Tapings: "The People Speak" - Press, 2007-2008; cuid15754 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Tapings: "The People Speak" - Reviews, 2008, undated; cuid15755 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Television: The People Speak - Press, 2009; cuid15756 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Television: "The People Speak" - Script (green script), Jan 2007; cuid15757 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Television: The People Speak - Viewer Reactions, Dec 2009, undated; cuid15758 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Television: A People's History of the United States - Correspondence, Jul 2006-Aug 2006; cuid15759 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Television: A People's History of the United States: Development Proposals (Independent Production Fund), May 2006; cuid15760 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Television: A People's History of the United States: Letters of Interest, 1996-2001, undated; cuid15761 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Television: A People's History of the United States: Treatments (12 episodes), undated; cuid15762 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Treatments: "Stop-Off at Ludlow" or "The Train to Trinadad" or "A Western Story" (working titles for "Purgatory River"), undated; cuid15763 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Series IV: Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1964-2008
  This series documents many of Howard Zinn's appearances and speaking engagements including lectures, speeches, panel participation, Congressional hearings, radio broadcasts, trial testimony and awards ceremonies. Arranged chronologically by the date of each event, materials may include correspondence, flyers and advertisements, press, contracts/agreements, notes and a few speech transcripts. In some cases, there is only a letter requesting his participation, annotated with the word "No".
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements (includes letter from Abbie Hoffman), 1964-1965; cuid15764 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1966; cuid15765 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1967; cuid15766 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1968; cuid15767 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1969; cuid15768 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1970; cuid15769 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1971-1972; cuid15770 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1973-1975; cuid15771 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1976-1977; cuid15772 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1978-1979; cuid15773 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1980; cuid15774 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1981; cuid15775 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1982; cuid15776 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements (includes Zinn testimony at Congressional Hearings on Defense Spending and letter from Ron Dellums), 1982; cuid15777 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1983; cuid15778 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1984; cuid15779 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1985; cuid15780 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1986; cuid15781 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1987; cuid15782 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1988; cuid15783 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1989; cuid15784 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1990; cuid15785 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Jan 1991-Apr 1991; cuid15786 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, May 1991-Dec 1991; cuid15787 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Jan 1992-Sep 1992; cuid15788 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Oct 1992; cuid15789 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Nov 1992-Dec 1992; cuid15790 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1993; cuid15791 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Jan 1994-Jun 1994; cuid15792 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Jul 1994-Dec 1994; cuid15793 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements (includes letter from John Conyers Jr.), 1995; cuid15794 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1996; cuid15795 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1997; cuid15796 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1998; cuid15797 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1999; cuid15798 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2000; cuid15799 (Box 18, Folder 10)